
// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers

let questions = [

    {

    numb: 1,

    question: "C Language was developed in the year ____?",

    answer: "1970",

    options: [

      "1970",

      "1975",

      "1980",

      "1985",

    ]

  },

    {

    numb: 2,

    question: " What is the 16-bit compiler allowable range for integer constants?",

    answer: "-32768 to 32767",

    options: [

      "-3.4e38 to 3.4e38",

      "-32767 to 32768",

      "-32668 to 32667",

      "-32768 to 32767"

    ]

  },

    {

    numb: 3,

    question: "What is required in each C program?",

    answer: "The program must have at least one function.",

    options: [

 "The program must have at least one function.",

"The program does not require any function.",

"Input data",

"Output data",

    ]

  },

    {

    numb: 4,

    question: "Which one is not a reserve keyword in C Language?",

    answer: "main",

    options: [

      "auto",

      "case",

      "main",

      "resister"

    ]

  },

    {

    numb: 5,

    question: "Prototype of a function means?",

    answer: "Declaration of Function",

    options: [

      "Name of Function",

      "Output of Function",

      "Declaration of Function",

      "Input of Function",

    ]

  },

  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question

  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  {

   numb: 6,

   question: "Name the loop that executes at least once",

    answer: "do-while",

   options: [

   "while ",

   "do-while",

   "if-else",

   "for"

    ]

  },

    {

   numb: 7,

   question: "Far pointer can access ___",

    answer: "All Memory Location",

   options: [

   "Single Memory Location",

   "No Memory Location",

   "All Memory Location",

   "Frist And Last Memory Address"

    ]

  },

  {

   numb: 8,

   question: "An uninitialized pointer in C is called ___",

    answer: "Wild Pointer",

   options: [

   "Constructor",

   "Dangling Pointer",

   "Wild Pointer",

   "Destructor"

    ]

  },

  {

   numb: 9,

   question: "A pointer that is pointing to NOTHING is called ____",

    answer: "NULL Pointer",

   options: [

   "VOID Pointer",

   "Dangling Pointer",

   "NULL Pointer",

   "WILD pointer"

    ]

  },

    {

   numb: 10,

   question: "What is a format specifier in C language.?",

    answer: "All the above",

   options: [

   "A format Specifier tells compiler to treat a variable value is predefined way.",

   "Different format specifiers are used to print different type of data. ",

   "Format specifiers are used to write data to files in a formatted way.",

   "All the above"

    ]

  },

];
